developershed.com 1999-11-17

# ngenuity NETWORK - Privacy Statement

**NGENUITY Privacy Statement**

NGENUITY has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices the NGENUITY Network of websites, including DevShed.com, 32bit.com and penguinfiles.com.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address may be used to gather broad demographic information. Such information enables us to better tailor our content to our users needs and to help our advertisers better understand the demographics of our audience.

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

 **Advertising**  
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. Cookies are not required to view any NGENUITY website, and any user may opt not to use them by disabling the use of cookies in their browser. Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies. **Public Forums**  
This site makes forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to our users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. **Mailing List**  
This site maitains a mailing list. NGENUITY gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list at any time by following the instructions provided in every newsletter.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

NGENUITY
